



Adrian Ivan

Date of birth: 06/01/2000 | **Nationality:** Romanian | **Phone number:**

(+40) 758914900 (Mobile) | **Email address:** adivan0601@gmail.com

Address: Baia Mare, Romania (Home)

ABOUT ME

My name is Adrian Ivan, I am 23 years old and I graduated from the Faculty of Informatics and Economics. During my studies, I acquired solid knowledge in the fields of Frontend and Design. Every day I like to learn new things and this fields are the best for that. In addition, through Frontend, the code I wrote can be very useful for other people. I consider that I am sociable, punctual, a good organizer, quick in different tasks and I like working in a team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

15/05/2023 - 15/09/2023 Baia Mare, Romania

ACCOUNTANT SC EXPERTISE CONSULTING IVN SRL

- financial department
- entering invoices, receipt, preparing balances, payment statements

01/03/2021 - CURRENT Baia Mare, Romania

ADMINISTRATOR / DISPATCHER SC ADIVAN SPEDITION SRL

- company administration
- relations with clients
- · coordinate the deliveries
- negociation
- · financial department

10/11/2020 – CURRENT Baia Mare, Romania

DISPATCHER / COURIER SC MEDIACURIER TEAM SRL

- collaboration contract with SC ADIVAN SPEDITION SRL
- coordinate routes
- fast delivery packages
- social media manager
- · website / logo / flyers / business card designer

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/10/2019 - 15/07/2022 Baia Mare, Romania

COLLEGE GRADUATE Universitatea Tehnica din Cluj Napoca

Field of study Informatics - economy

14/09/2015 - 15/07/2019 Baia Mare, Romania

HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATE Colegiul National "Vasile Lucaciu"

Field of study Math - Informatics, English bilingual

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **ROMANIAN**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	C1	C1	C1	C1	C1
GERMAN	A2	A2	A2	A2	A2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

Microsoft Office | Social Media | WEB: Web Designer, Web Developer | Html, Java, CSS | Content editing tools (Canva; Adobe Premiere Pro) | Graphic Design (Adobe Spark, Photopea, Canva)

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

PROJECTS

07/2022 - CURRENT

Personal site My personal portfolio so far

Link https://adivan06.github.io/portfolio/

01/2023 - 02/2023

Delivery company This website is presenting a local delivery company, including their list of prices, why to choose them and how to contact them for a delivery.

Link https://adivan06.github.io/Mediacurier/

07/2022 - 09/2022

Only library Through this web page, I tried to use all the knowledge from the tutorials I went through. The page contains HTML and CSS

Link https://adivan06.github.io/library/

01/2022 - 02/2022

Transport app/site The site contains an application that calculates the profitability of the transport according to the variables you enter in a form. To create this application I used: HTML and CSS - for the apperance of the site, JavaScript - for functionality, MySQL - data storage in a database

TRAININGS

CodeAcademy tutorials

I went through some tutorials on the CodeAcademy platform because I wanted to deepen my knowledge of HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Frontend Simplified

Link https://frontendsimplified.com/